"See spoons for more."
(Bernadette:)What could it be?
"We are Groot"?
"We are the champions"?
"We are family"?
"I got all my sisters with me."
(Howard:)Are you serious?
(Bernadette:)Yeah.
(Howard:)Are you sure?
(Bernadette:)Pretty positive.
(Bernadette:)That's a joke, because
the pregnancy test says...
(Howard:)Oh, my God.
(Howard:)This is incredible.
(Howard:)We're gonna be parents?
(Howard:)We're gonna get
to board planes first.
(Howard:)Finally gonna get to see
(Howard:)what's in that family bathroom
at the mall.
(Bernadette:)I know, it's crazy.
(Howard:)It is crazy.
(Howard:)Oh.
(Howard:)I mean, how do you... prepare
for something like this?
(Howard:)I'm not even sure
I've held a baby before.
(Bernadette:)Oh, it's okay,
you'll figure it out.